{
    "questions": [

        {
            "questionText": "Csoloh",
            "description": "A place to study!",
            "answers": "school",
            "ans":"",
            "id":0
        }
        , {
            "questionText": "Aerk",
            "description": "A cleaning tool",
            "answers": "rake",
            "ans":"",
            "id":1
        }
        , {
            "questionText": "Feriaergotrr",
            "description": "An household appliance",
            "answers": "refrigerator",
            "ans":"",
            "id":2
        }
        , {
            "questionText": "Hpneoeelt",
            "description": "Connecting people",
            "answers": "telephone",
            "ans":"",
            "id":3
        }
        , {
            "questionText": "Appre",
            "description": "Something to write",
            "answers": "paper",
            "ans":"",
            "id":4
        }
        , {
            "questionText": "Uhbsr",
            "description": "rub it to clean it",
            "answers": "brush",
            "ans":"",
            "id":5
         }
        , {
            "questionText": "Amigicna",
            "description": "A person with superior powers",
            "answers": "magician",
            "ans":"",
            "id":6
         }
        , {
            "questionText": "Soiphalt",
            "description": "a place for treatment",
            "answers": "hospital",
            "ans":"",
            "id":7
        }
        , {
            "questionText": "Crkut",
            "description": "used for carrying goods",
            "answers": "truck",
            "ans":"",
            "id":8
        }
        , {
            "questionText": "Macle",
            "description": "An animal",
            "answers": "camel",
            "ans":"",
            "id":9
        }


    ],
    "type": "Easy"
}
